<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2. Get started with OCI Services on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/</link><description>Recent content in 2. Get started with OCI Services on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2.1 Creating an Oracle Cloud Free Tier Account</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/1/</guid><description>2.1 Creating an Oracle Cloud Free Tier Account To try Oracle Cloud Infrastructure for free, we provide a 30 day trial that&amp;rsquo;s available within the US 300$ limit. It is also free to use after 30 days for Always Free resources.
https://www.oracle.com/cloud/free/ List of available services in 30-day free trial https://www.oracle.com/cloud/free/#free-cloud-trial Procedure for creating an Oracle Cloud Free Tier account Free Tier Application Go to https://www.oracle.com/kr/cloud/free/ and click to start for free.</description></item><item><title>2.2 Connecting to the OCI Console</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/2/</guid><description>2.2 Connecting to the OCI Console Method #1. Connect via Welcome Email 1 . When you receive your Free Tier Account ready mail, click Sign in to Oracle Cloud to connect to OCI Cloud Console.
On the login screen, enter the administrator email and password you entered when you applied for Free Tier to log in. Login successful Method #2. Connect directly to your browser Connect to https://cloud.oracle.com via your browser to login to Oracle Cloud.</description></item><item><title>2.3 Using the OCI Console</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/3/</guid><description>2.3 Using the OCI Console OCI Console UI Service Navigation You can work with services and resources through the navigation menus in the upper left corner.
Region Administration Your current Region is displayed in the upper right, and if you subscribe to and use multiple Regions, you can switch to a different Region from that menu. In addition, if you want to subscribe to another Region, you can subscribe through the Region Admin menu in the submenu.</description></item><item><title>2.4 Initial Cloud Account (Tenancy) Architecture</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/4/</guid><description>2.4 Initial Cloud Account (Tenancy) Architecture Once the Cloud Account environment is created, users will be managed by OCI Native IAM. Oracle Identity Cloud Service (IDCS) was initially Federtion as an Identity Provider as a relic of OCI Classic. Administrator of OCI has all privileges of the OCI Tenancy The OCI_Administrator group in IDCS is mapped to an Administrator group in OCI. When you log into OCI Console as SSO, you are actually a user in OCI_Administrator, but on OCI they are treated as Administrator groups and have related permissions.</description></item></channel></rss>