<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>9. Machine Image on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 9. Machine Image on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>9.1 OS Image provided by default</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/1/</guid>
      <description>9.1 OS Image provided by default It provides OS image and application image for creating Compute Instance, and you can also create Instance through Custom Image and Boot Volumes created by the user. As shown in the figure, it is a list of currently provided OS images that can be selected from the image selection menu on the right when creating a Compute Instance. Image provided [Platform Images] (https://docs.cloud.oracle.com/iaas/Content/Compute/References/images.htm)&#xA;Oracle Images</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.2 Create Custom Image from Instance</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/2/</guid>
      <description>9.2 Create Custom Image from Instance Important The instance goes offline for a few minutes while the image is being created. It is recommended to stop the instance while creating a custom image, and if you proceed while it is running, it is forcibly stopped. Interruptions can cause problems with your data Even if the target instance to create a Custom Image is equipped with a Block Volume, only the Boot Volume is included when creating a Custom Image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.3 Custom Image Export/Import</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/3/</guid>
      <description>9.3 Custom Image Export/Import Custom Image provides import and export functions. The Custom Image belongs to the Comparment within the Region, and to copy it to another Compartment or to another Region, it is exported to Object Storage and then imported again at the desired location.&#xA;For the description of creating a Bucket in Object Storage and pre-authentication, see [7. Using Object Storage] (/oci/chapter07/).&#xA;Custom Image Export Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
