<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>15.1 Using the Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/1/</guid>
      <description>15.1 Using Resource Manager Resource Manager is a service that registers and runs Terraform Configuration as a function to automate OCI resource provisioning. Instead of installing Terraform on the client, you can register Terraform Configuration files in Resource Manager and run it with the OCI console or OCI CLI.&#xA;The difference is that the Terraform CLI does not need to be installed separately, and the Terraform execution state is managed by the Resource Manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13.1 Preparation for Autoscaling</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter13/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter13/1/</guid>
      <description>13.1 Preparation for Autoscaling Create an instance for Autoscaling Autoscaling requires a reference image. Let&amp;rsquo;s create an image with Apache installed on Oracle Linux used in the Load Balancer chapter so that one additional instance of Apache can be started for server extension through Autoscaling. Also consider using cloud-init, considering how to get the latest sources for additional instances to run. At this time, to make it easier to confirm that it is an additional instance, the private IP of the created host is visible in index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.1 Enabling Compute Instance Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/1/</guid>
      <description>12.1 Enable Compute Instance Monitoring Enable Monitoring Below I used the latest Oracle Linux image with OracleCloudAgent already installed.&#xA;Go to the detail page of the Compute instance you want to monitor.&#xA;Select Resources &amp;gt; Metrics in the lower left&#xA;Click Enable Monitoring to enable monitoring Boot Volumes, Block Volumes, VNICs Metric information is basically collected for other services that support monitoring except Compute. Check monitoring of resources mounted on Compute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.1 OS Image provided by default</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/1/</guid>
      <description>9.1 OS Image provided by default It provides OS image and application image for creating Compute Instance, and you can also create Instance through Custom Image and Boot Volumes created by the user. As shown in the figure, it is a list of currently provided OS images that can be selected from the image selection menu on the right when creating a Compute Instance. Image provided [Platform Images] (https://docs.cloud.oracle.com/iaas/Content/Compute/References/images.htm)&#xA;Oracle Images</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.1 Creating a Bucket</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/1/</guid>
      <description>7.1 Creating Buckets Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Object Storage &amp;amp; Archive Storage &amp;gt; Buckets.&#xA;Select the compartment in which to create a bucket.&#xA;Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to [Core Infrastructure] &amp;gt; [Object Storage] &amp;gt; [Storage]&#xA;Click Create Bucket.&#xA;Enter creation information&#xA;Bucket Name: Enter the name of the bucket to be created, ex) &amp;ldquo;ExampleBucket&amp;rdquo; Default Storage Tier: Standard: It is used to store frequently used data quickly with standard object storage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.1 Creating a Reserved Public IP</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter04/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter04/1/</guid>
      <description>4.1 Create Reserved Public IP Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;gt; IP Management &amp;gt; Reserved Public IPs.&#xA;Click Reserve Public IP Address.&#xA;Enter creation information&#xA;Name: Enter the name of the Reserved Public IP to be created&#xA;Compartment: Select the Compartment to be placed, ex) select &amp;ldquo;Sandbox&amp;rdquo;&#xA;IP Address Source: If you have BYOIP, you can select it, but if there is no other BYOIP, select Oracle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.1 Creating a Work Compartment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/1/</guid>
      <description>3.1 Creating a Work Compartment A compartment can be thought of as a folder structure as a logical concept that makes it easy to manage resources. When a tenancy is created, the first Root Compartment is created, and administrators can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources fall into a specific Compartment and can manage the access policies of their users in units of Compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.5.1 Access from Linux, Mac</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/5/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/5/1/</guid>
      <description>3.5.1 Access from Linux, Mac Keys generated by ssh-keygen in the Privacy Enhanced Mail (PEM) file format are ready for Linux and Mac. The .ppk generated by the PuTTY Key Generator is used by the converter to convert to PEM format.&#xA;Connecting a Linux instance from a UNIX-style system Change Personal Key Permissions&#xA;$ chmod 400 &amp;lt;private_key&amp;gt; &amp;lt;private_key&amp;gt;: Private key matching public key registered in Linux instance Connect via SSH command</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.1 Creating a Block Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/1/</guid>
      <description>3.6.1 Creating Block Volumes Block Volumes are network storage for use with OCI Compute Instances. By creating a Block Volume, attaching it to your instance, and mounting it, you can use it as if you were using a physical hard drive attached to your computer. If it can be mounted on one instance at a time, it can be mounted on another instance after dismounting.&#xA;Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.7.1 Backing up Block Volumes</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/1/</guid>
      <description>3.7.1 Backing up Block Volume Full If you deleted the Block Volume in the previous guide, create it again.&#xA;Backing up the default Block Volume Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes.&#xA;Click the name of the Block Volume you want to back up.&#xA;On the Block Volume detail page, click Resources &amp;gt; Block Volume Backups in the lower left corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.8.1 Backing Up Boot Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/1/</guid>
      <description>3.8.1 Backing up Boot Volume The Boot Volume backup function is almost identical to the Block Volume backup function.&#xA;Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to the Boot Volume detail page.&#xA;Method #1 Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances. Click the target instance VM. Go to Resources &amp;gt; Boot volume and click the Attached Boot Volume to go to the detail page. Method #2 Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Volume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.1 Regions, Availability Domains</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/1/</guid>
      <description>1.1 Regions, Availability Domains Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI) is hosted in Region and Availability Domain. Region is a geographical area and Availability Domain is a data center located in one region. A single Region consists of one or more Availability Domain.&#xA;Availability domains are separated from each other so that they are not affected by defects at the same time or by defects in other Availability domains.Availability Domain is designed so that it does not affect other Availability domains because it does not share resources such as power, cooling and internal networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.1 Creating an Oracle Cloud Free Tier Account</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/1/</guid>
      <description>2.1 Creating an Oracle Cloud Free Tier Account To try Oracle Cloud Infrastructure for free, we provide a 30 day trial that&amp;rsquo;s available within the US 300$ limit. It is also free to use after 30 days for Always Free resources.&#xA;https://www.oracle.com/cloud/free/ List of available services in 30-day free trial https://www.oracle.com/cloud/free/#free-cloud-trial Procedure for creating an Oracle Cloud Free Tier account Free Tier Application Go to https://www.oracle.com/kr/cloud/free/ and click to start for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.1 Example File Storage Configuration</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/1/</guid>
      <description>8.1 Example of File Storage Configuration A shared file system between servers, file storage allows multiple client servers to share files. In order to understand the necessary security rules, let&amp;rsquo;s configure File Storage on a separate subnet from the default VCN&amp;rsquo;s subnet as shown in the figure below.&#xA;Security List&#xA;In the figure below, the source IP is designated as the CIDR of the VCN to allow access from a specific subnet on the VCN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.1 Load Balancer Configuration Example</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/1/</guid>
      <description>10.1 Load Balancer configuration example To ensure the availability of instances, you can load balance across multiple target servers via OCI Load Balancer. Target servers are also typically configured in different ADs or in different Fault Domains on the same AD to ensure availability. And the OCI Load Balancer itself is configured redundantly for Fail Over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.1 Compartment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/1/</guid>
      <description>6.1 Compartment A compartment is a logical concept that makes it easy to manage resources, and you can think of it as a folder structure. When a Tenancy is created, one Root Compartment is created for the first time, and an administrator can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources belong to a specific compartment, and users&amp;rsquo; access policies can be managed in units of compartments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15.2 Stack Template for Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/2/</guid>
      <description>15.2 Stack Template for Resource Manager Stack Template In the OCI console, click Developer Services &amp;gt; Resource Manager &amp;gt; Stacks in the navigation menu.&#xA;Click Create Stack.&#xA;Select the second Template option and click Select Template.&#xA;You can see the templates we are providing.&#xA;Quickstarts&#xA;Service&#xA;Architect&#xA;Private&#xA;It is empty for now, but you can use the template to be shared within Tenancy by registering a private template.&#xA;Deploy to Oracle Cloud In the future, you will see buttons like the one below in the OCI documentation and OCI example sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.2 Creating Monitoring Alarm</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/2/</guid>
      <description>12.2 Creating Monitoring Alarm Let&amp;rsquo;s create an alarm to send an email when CPU utilization reaches a specified number among monitoring set on Compute instance.&#xA;Defined in Observability &amp;amp; Management &amp;gt; Monitoring &amp;gt; Alarm Definition in the navigation menu in the OCI console Defined in the options menu of the resource monitoring metric There are two methods above, but in this document, we will proceed to the second method, which is easy to use because the alarm&amp;rsquo;s metric is automatically set as the selected monitoring metric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.3.1 Installing Grafana on Compute VM</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/1/</guid>
      <description>12.3.1 Install Grafana on Compute VM Create Compute Instance Go to the Compute Instance creation screen. Select the image source as the Oracle Linux Cloud Developer Image image from the Oracle Images list. Oracle Cloud Developer Image has development tools such as OCI CLI already installed. Create a Compute instance. Copy the OCID of the created Compute instance. OCI CLI - Instance Principal Settings In order to use the OCI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.3.2 Grafana Configuration</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/2/</guid>
      <description>12.3.2 Grafana Configuration Register Data Source Log in to Grafana.&#xA;Go to left menu Configuration &amp;gt; Data Sources, or click Add data source on the home dashboard. Select Oracle Cloud Infrastructure among data sources OCI Data Source Settings&#xA;Tenancy OCID: Log in to the OCI Console, check and enter the Tenancy OCID Default Region: Select the desired Region Environment: Select OCI Instance Click Save &amp;amp; Test to check if the connection is successful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13.2 Configuring Autoscaling</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter13/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter13/2/</guid>
      <description>13.2 Autoscaling Configuration The following are required for autoscaling.&#xA;Instance Pool: Autoscaling automatically changes the current number of instances in the Instance Pool according to a set metric, and an Instance Pool is required. Enable Monitoring: Compute instances are monitored and based on resource status, Monitoring must be enabled. Service Limit: You must have enough relevant resources to start a new instance with Autoscaling. Autoscaling settings Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.2 Mounting and using FSS on a Linux VM</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/2/</guid>
      <description>8.2 Mounting and using FSS (File Storage Service) on a Linux VM Constraints Even if File Storage is the same subnet as Compute Instance, the following rules must be set in the Security List to open the File Storage firewall. Create Subnet Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;gt; Virtual Cloud Networks.&#xA;Click on ExampleVCN, the VCN you created earlier.&#xA;Click Create Subnets&#xA;Enter creation information: Enter only bold text fields and use default values ​​for the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.2 Create Custom Image from Instance</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/2/</guid>
      <description>9.2 Create Custom Image from Instance Important The instance goes offline for a few minutes while the image is being created. It is recommended to stop the instance while creating a custom image, and if you proceed while it is running, it is forcibly stopped. Interruptions can cause problems with your data Even if the target instance to create a Custom Image is equipped with a Block Volume, only the Boot Volume is included when creating a Custom Image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.2 Uploading Files to Bucket</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/2/</guid>
      <description>7.2 Uploading Files to Bucket Object Storage supports up to 50 GB per single file. Based on the message of the OCI Console, you can only upload up to 2 GiB. Files larger than that can be uploaded via the SDK or API.&#xA;Upload file to Bucket from OCI Console Click on the Bucket name to view details.&#xA;Click Upload.&#xA;When the dialog box appears, you can drag and drop the file or upload it through the browser file upload function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2 Allocating Reserved Public IP</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter04/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter04/2/</guid>
      <description>4.2 Allocating Reserved Public IP Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.&#xA;From the list of instances, click the name of the instance to assign a static IP to to move to details.&#xA;Click Resources &amp;gt; Attached VNICs in the lower left.&#xA;A list of connected virtual network interface cards (VNICs) is displayed, and one Primary VNIC created by default is displayed as shown below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.2 Creating Users</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/2/</guid>
      <description>6.2 Create User Tips Users who can access OCI are mainly IDCS users and OCI users. OCI is connected to Identity Cloud Service by default, so IDCS users can be federated and logged in. And IDCS is not registered, it has its own users only in OCI. The content here is intended only for users of OCI itself. Add OCI Manager Step 1. Add OCI Manager Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.2 Creating a VCN for a Virtual Network Environment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/2/</guid>
      <description>3.2 Creating a VCN for a Virtual Network Environment What is a Virtual Cloud Network (VCN)? Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) provides a virtual network environment. You can configure the VCN and its resources to suit your needs, thus configuring several forms of virtual network environment. A subnet is created as a sub-element of a VCN as a unit of a single Availability Domain. Depending on the route table, subnets move traffic to the destination path, and subnets can control incoming and outgoing traffic to the security list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.2 Mounting Block Volume to Instance</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/2/</guid>
      <description>3.6.2 Mounting Block Volume to Instance Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.&#xA;Click on the name of the target Instance you created earlier.&#xA;On the Instance detail page, click Resources &amp;gt; Attached block volumes in the lower left corner.&#xA;Click the Attached block volumes button&#xA;In the dialog that appears, select Next.&#xA;Volume: Select the desired Block Volume from the list in the compartment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.7.2 Creating a New Volume from Backup</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/2/</guid>
      <description>3.7.2 Create a new volume with backup This is a recovery method that creates a new Block Volume using the Block Volume backup. The restored Block Volume can be used by mounting it on the Compute Instance in the same way as installing a new Block Volume.&#xA;Create a new Block Volume from backup Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes Backups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.8.2 Creating a New Boot Volume from a Backup</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/2/</guid>
      <description>3.8.2 Create a new Boot Volume from backup The Boot Volume backup recovery function is almost identical to the Block Volume backup recovery function.&#xA;Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to the Boot Volume detail page.&#xA;On the Boot Volume detail page, click Resources &amp;gt; Boot Volume Backups in the lower left corner.&#xA;Click Restore Boot Volume in the action menu on the right of the desired backup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.2 Connecting to the OCI Console</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/2/</guid>
      <description>2.2 Connecting to the OCI Console Method #1. Connect via Welcome Email 1 . When you receive your Free Tier Account ready mail, click Sign in to Oracle Cloud to connect to OCI Cloud Console.&#xA;On the login screen, enter the administrator email and password you entered when you applied for Free Tier to log in. Login successful Method #2. Connect directly to your browser Connect to https://cloud.oracle.com via your browser to login to Oracle Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.2 VCN Configuration</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/2/</guid>
      <description>10.2 VCN Configuration Create VCN for LoadBalancer test Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking » Virtual Cloud Networks.&#xA;In the lower left compartment, click Sandbox.&#xA;Click Start VCN Wizard&#xA;Select Create VCN with Internet Connectivity and click Start VCN Wizard again&#xA;As described in the figure, the selected one includes Public and Private Subnet, and communicates with the Internet through Internat Gateway and NAT Gateway, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.5.2 Connecting to PuTTY on Windows</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/5/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/5/2/</guid>
      <description>3.5.2 Connecting to PuTTY on Windows The SSH Key generated by the PuTTY Key Generator is stored as PuTTY Private Key (PPK) .ppk via Save private key and used by PuTTY. Keys generated by ssh-keygen in the Privacy Enhanced Mail (PEM) file format are available at PuTTY via PEM -&amp;gt; PPK conversion.&#xA;Install PuTTY If PuTTY is not installed, download and install a putty from http://www.putty.org/ .&#xA;Connecting a Linux Instance on Windows Run putty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Fault Domains</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/2/</guid>
      <description>1.2 Fault Domains A Fault Domain is a grouping of hardware and infrastructure within an Availability Domain. Each Availability Domain has three Fault Domains. Fault Domains ensure that compute instances are not distributed across one physical hardware within a single Availability Domain. Hardware failures or hardware maintenance within one Fault Domain do not affect other Fault Domains.&#xA;When creating a new Compute instance, users can select a Fault Domain. If not selected by the user, the system automatically assigns them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15.3 Configuring a Private Git Server for Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/3/</guid>
      <description>15.3 Configuring Private Git Server for Resource Manager Resource Manager supports GitHub and GitLab as Terraform configuration repositories. Environments that can be accessed through the public Internet can of course be connected from Resource Manager. If you want to use an internal server instead of a public server for setting storage, you can connect to a privately installed server on OCI by following the procedure below.&#xA;Create Private GitLab CE VM Create Compute instance Create a Compute instance on which to install GitLab CE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13.3 Autoscaling Test</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter13/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter13/3/</guid>
      <description>13.3 Autoscaling Test Scale Out occurrence test Go to the Instance Pool and connect to the current Compute instance with SSH.&#xA;Install the stress tool&#xA;sudo yum-config-manager --enable ol7_developer_EPEL sudo yum install -y stress Perform stress&#xA;sudo stress --cpu N Execution example&#xA;Continue to apply the load by adjusting the number of CPUs of the Compute Instance to be used. Considering the Cool Down value determined when auto-scale is set, apply a load longer than that time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 Export Option for Access Control</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/3/</guid>
      <description>8.3 Export Option for Access Control Permission control through Export Option setting Move to the detail screen of the file system created earlier. Click Export created in the Export list as shown in the figure below.&#xA;At the bottom of the Export detail screen, NFS Export Options are displayed as shown in the figure.&#xA;The default created option is accessible as Read/Write from all clients (0.0.0.0/0).&#xA;Click Edit NFS Export Options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3 Object Permission Management - Pre-authentication</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/3/</guid>
      <description>7.3 Object Permission Management - Pre-Authenticated Requests Pre-Authenticated Requests is a function that allows users to access buckets or objects without authentication. It is created as a temporary shared link that allows you to access the Bucket or Object without authentication until the specified period. This shared link will make it accessible to any user.&#xA;Access to Object URL In the Object Details screen, check the URL path of the object.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.7.3 Copying Backups to Another Region</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/3/</guid>
      <description>3.7.3 Copying Backup to Another Region Block Volume backup is only possible within a single Region. If it is needed in another region for disaster recovery or other purposes, it can be copied to another region through the inter-region copy function.&#xA;Constraints Cross-region backup copies have some limitations. See the official documentation for exact details.&#xA;Limitations for Copying Volume Backups Across Regions Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes Backups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.3 Creating a Key Pair for SSH Connections</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/3/</guid>
      <description>3.3 Creating a Key Pair for SSH Connections Use SSH Key Pair instead of password to access the server instance. Key pair consists of a private key and a public key, the private key is kept on the user&amp;rsquo;s computer, and the public key must be registered when the server instance is created.&#xA;To create a key pair, you need a key generation tool, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you&amp;rsquo;ll use it after installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.5.3 Changing the PEM &lt;-&gt; PPK Format</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/5/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/5/3/</guid>
      <description>3.5.3 Changing the PEM &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; PPK Format Privacy Enhanced Mail (PEM) Generated via ssh-keygen command based on an earlier document in the key pair format used by an OCI instance&#xA;PuTTY Private Key (PPK) The key format used by PuTTY, which is a format created by default when saved through PuTTY Key Generator&#xA;PEM to PPK format conversion 1 . PuTTY Post-install Key Generator (http://www.putty.org/) 2. Run the PuTTY Key Generator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.3 Connecting to Block Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/3/</guid>
      <description>3.6.3 Connecting to Block Volume After mounting the Block Volume, you need to establish an iSCSI connection. It is executed by the iscsiadm command, and the command to be executed is provided by the mounted Block Volume, so you can copy it and run it as it is.&#xA;Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.&#xA;Click on the name of the target Instance you created earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.8.3 Creating a New Instance with Boot Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/3/</guid>
      <description>3.8.3 Creating a New Instance with Boot Volume You can create a new Compute Instance using a Boot Volume that is not already in use for the Instance.&#xA;Create a new instance with Boot Volume Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.&#xA;Check the Region to create an instance for and click Create Instance.&#xA;Choose the image you want to use&#xA;Click Edit in Image and Shape to change the image source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.3 Using the OCI Console</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/3/</guid>
      <description>2.3 Using the OCI Console OCI Console UI Service Navigation You can work with services and resources through the navigation menus in the upper left corner.&#xA;Region Administration Your current Region is displayed in the upper right, and if you subscribe to and use multiple Regions, you can switch to a different Region from that menu. In addition, if you want to subscribe to another Region, you can subscribe through the Region Admin menu in the submenu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.3 Creating a Backend Web Server</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/3/</guid>
      <description>10.3 Creating a Backend Web Server Create your first Linux Instance Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute » Instances.&#xA;Check the Region to create an instance for and click Create Instance.&#xA;Enter creation information&#xA;Enter the necessary values ​​for only the main items and accept the default values ​​for the rest.&#xA;Basic Information&#xA;Name: Enter a name, for example “Webserver1” Create in compartment: Select the compartment to be located, select the previously created Sandbox Image and Shape</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.3 Creating Groups</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/3/</guid>
      <description>6.3 Create a group Step 1. Add OCI group Log in to the OCI console as administrator. Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Identity &amp;amp; Security &amp;gt; Identity &amp;gt; Groups. After creating Cloud Account, you can see that there is only one Administrators group. Click Create Group Enter group information Name: Enter &amp;ldquo;SandboxGroup&amp;rdquo; Description: Enter a description, Ex) same name as &amp;ldquo;SandboxGroup&amp;rdquo; Click Create Step 2. Add User to Group Click the created group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Compartment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/3/</guid>
      <description>1.3 Compartment Compartments are a folder structure that makes it easy to manage resources. When a tenancy is created, the first Root Compartment is created, and administrators can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources fall into a specific Compartment and can manage the access policies of their users in units of Compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.4 Snapshot for Backup</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/4/</guid>
      <description>8.4 Snapshot for backup You can create a Snapshot of the File System based on the time it was executed. You can recover files or all of them from the created Snapshot.&#xA;Snapshot #1 Connect to the tested VM.&#xA;Copy one file to the mounted file system.&#xA;[opc@examplelinuxinstance ~]$ cd /mnt/FSS-Storage/ [opc@examplelinuxinstance FSS-Storage]$wget https://github.com/oracle/oci-cli/releases/download/v3.4.2/oci-cli-3.4.2-Oracle-Linux-7.9-Offline.zip ... 2022-01-14 06:04:59 (6.24 MB/s) - ‘oci-cli-3.4.2-Oracle-Linux-7.9-Offline.zip’ saved [42528311/42528311] [opc@examplelinuxinstance FSS-Storage]$ ls -la total 43025 drwxrwxrwx. 2 root root 3 Jan 14 06:04 .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.3 Custom Image Export/Import</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter09/3/</guid>
      <description>9.3 Custom Image Export/Import Custom Image provides import and export functions. The Custom Image belongs to the Comparment within the Region, and to copy it to another Compartment or to another Region, it is exported to Object Storage and then imported again at the desired location.&#xA;For the description of creating a Bucket in Object Storage and pre-authentication, see [7. Using Object Storage] (/oci/chapter07/).&#xA;Custom Image Export Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.4 Object Rights Management - Public Bucket</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/4/</guid>
      <description>7.4 Object Rights Management - Public Bucket The created Bucket is in Private state by default. Without authentication, access is not possible. If you change the Bucket to Public, you can access it without additional authentication. As with Pre-Authenticated Requests, a temporary shared link is not created, but access to the Bucket is allowed, allowing direct access to the object&amp;rsquo;s URL path.&#xA;Go to the detailed information screen of Bucket. You can check that Visibility is Private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.7.4 Backing up Policy-Based Block Volumes</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/4/</guid>
      <description>3.7.4 Backing up policy-based block volumes Volume Backup Policies Bronze Policy&#xA;Monthly - Monthly incremental backups run on the first day of each month. It is maintained for 12 months. Every year - A full backup is executed on January 1st of each year. It is maintained for 5 years. Silver Policy&#xA;Weekly - Weekly incremental backups run every Sunday. It is preserved for 4 weeks. Monthly - Monthly incremental backups run on the first day of each month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 Creating a Policy</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/4/</guid>
      <description>6.4 Creating Policy Step 1. Add Policy for the created group Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Identity &amp;amp; Security &amp;gt; Identity &amp;gt; Policies.&#xA;In the lower left, specify the target Compartment as Root Compartment.&#xA;Click Create Policy&#xA;Enter policy information&#xA;Name: Enter &amp;ldquo;SandboxPolicy&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Description: Enter a description, Ex) same name as &amp;ldquo;SandboxPolicy&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Policy Statements:&#xA;Select &amp;ldquo;Show manual editor&amp;rdquo; to input directly. Users in the SandboxGroup are set as follows to grant all permissions to the Sandbox Compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.4 Creating a Linux Instance</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/4/</guid>
      <description>3.4 Creating a Linux Instance tip It is a good idea to proactively check for sufficient resources before creating the instance. A Service Limit lookup is used to determine if there are resources available, particularly CPUs available, before creating an instance. In the OCI Console, open the navigation menu. Navigate to the Compute &amp;gt; Instances topic.&#xA;Verify the Region where you want to create the instance and click Create Instance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.4 Formatting Block Volumes</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/4/</guid>
      <description>3.6.4 Formatting Block Volumes After connecting to the Compute Instance with SSH, format the Block Volume. You can format the file system type by changing it to anything you want.&#xA;sudo mkfs -t &amp;lt;fs type&amp;gt; /dev/sdb Examples of execution&#xA;After looking up the Block Volume as shown below, it was formatted. [opc@examplelinuxinstance ~]$ lsblk -f NAME FSTYPE LABEL UUID MOUNTPOINT sdb sda ├─sda2 swap 7c02c8fa-405c-4583-bf26-72fcfff63ccf [SWAP] ├─sda3 xfs daec0eb0-26cf-43cb-bcb1-896cdc193242 / └─sda1 vfat 61E0-20B8 /boot/efi [opc@examplelinuxinstance ~]$ sudo mkfs -t xfs /dev/sdb meta-data=/dev/sdb isize=256 agcount=4, agsize=3276800 blks = sectsz=4096 attr=2, projid32bit=1 = crc=0 finobt=0, sparse=0, rmapbt=0 = reflink=0 data = bsize=4096 blocks=13107200, imaxpct=25 = sunit=0 swidth=0 blks naming =version 2 bsize=4096 ascii-ci=0, ftype=1 log =internal log bsize=4096 blocks=6400, version=2 = sectsz=4096 sunit=1 blks, lazy-count=1 realtime =none extsz=4096 blocks=0, rtextents=0 [opc@examplelinuxinstance ~]$ lsblk -f NAME FSTYPE LABEL UUID MOUNTPOINT sdb xfs c15dcf4c-e7af-4150-b1f8-07953032464a sda ├─sda2 swap 7c02c8fa-405c-4583-bf26-72fcfff63ccf [SWAP] ├─sda3 xfs daec0eb0-26cf-43cb-bcb1-896cdc193242 / └─sda1 vfat 61E0-20B8 /boot/efi </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.4 Initial Cloud Account (Tenancy) Architecture</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter02/4/</guid>
      <description>2.4 Initial Cloud Account (Tenancy) Architecture Once the Cloud Account environment is created, users will be managed by OCI Native IAM. Oracle Identity Cloud Service (IDCS) was initially Federtion as an Identity Provider as a relic of OCI Classic. Administrator of OCI has all privileges of the OCI Tenancy The OCI_Administrator group in IDCS is mapped to an Administrator group in OCI. When you log into OCI Console as SSO, you are actually a user in OCI_Administrator, but on OCI they are treated as Administrator groups and have related permissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.4 Creating a Subnet for a Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/4/</guid>
      <description>10.4 Create Subnet for Load Balancer Create Subnet Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking » Virtual Cloud Networks.&#xA;Click LoadBalancerVCN, the VCN you created earlier.&#xA;Click Create Subnets&#xA;Enter creation information: Enter only bold text fields and use default values ​​for the rest.&#xA;Name: Enter a name, Public LB Subnet Subnet Type: Select the default REGIONAL REGIONAL: This is a subnet that is globally located in the region, and has the advantage of being able to use the IP as it is in case of a Failover to another AD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.4 Virtual Cloud Network(VCN)</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/4/</guid>
      <description>1.4 Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) When you use OCI, one of the first things you need to do is create a Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) for other cloud resources. A virtual network environment that is used by server resources in Oracle data centers, such as network address allocation, firewalls, routing rules, gateways, and so on.&#xA;If you configure the auto-created method when you first create your VCN, the following default configuration will be created:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.5 Hosting Static Websites with Public Bucket</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/5/</guid>
      <description>7.5 Static Website Hosting via Public Bucket If we create a public bucket, we will use that it can be accessed by a URL path, and we will try to host a simple static website using dots. Object Storage is basically a date structure without a hierarchical structure. Let&amp;rsquo;s test how to handle web pages with folder structure&#xA;Constraints As of the current version, Public Bucket can be used for file link sharing, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.5 Mount Block Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/5/</guid>
      <description>3.6.5 Mount Block Volume According to the OCI document, if there are two or more volume other than root volume, if the device name is mounted with the device name, the device name and the actual device may be different.As of January 10, 2019, the CONSISTENT Device Path function was released to ensure the response of the device after the server reversion and the actual device.In the unsupported images and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.5 Creating a Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/5/</guid>
      <description>10.5 Creating a Load Balancer Create Load Balancer Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;gt; Load Balancers.&#xA;Click Create Load Balancer.&#xA;Select Load Balancer as the type.&#xA;Load Balancer Type: Used when distributing to HTTP listeners as L7 load balancers. Network Load Balancer Type: L4 load balancer, used to distribute to general IP and Port. Enter basic creation information&#xA;Name: Enter Load Balancer name, Ex) ExampleLB</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.5 Grabbing the Policy Concept</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/5/</guid>
      <description>6.5 Getting the Policy Concept IAM Policy IAM Policy is an access policy for OCI resources. A policy can generally be thought of as defining what grants a user group permission to a specific type of resource belonging to a specific compartment.&#xA;Policy syntax All policies have the following syntax.&#xA;Allow &amp;lt;subject&amp;gt; to &amp;lt;verb&amp;gt; &amp;lt;resource-type&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;location&amp;gt; where &amp;lt;conditions&amp;gt; For detailed syntax, please refer to OCI Documentation.&#xA;https://docs.cloud.oracle.com/iaas/Content/Identity/Concepts/policysyntax.htm&#xA;Policy General Format If the permissions for resources are defined through the policy below, all permissions are granted to the administrator when creating a tenancy, and general users and groups that do not apply a separate policy have no permissions at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5 Bare Metal, Virtual Machine</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/5/</guid>
      <description>1.5 Bare Metal, Virtual Machine OCI offers both Bare Metal and Virtual Machine instances&#xA;Bare Metal: Provides an environment where physical servers can be dedicated to a single user. By using the resources of the physical server directly and dedicatedly, we utilize 100% of the server resources to deliver high performance. Virtual Machine: Provides a computing environment through virtualization on a physical server. By going through a layer virtualized by the hypervisor, it offers relatively lower performance than bare metal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.6 Uploading Files via CloudBerry Explorer</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/6/</guid>
      <description>7.6 Uploading Files via CloudBerry Explorer Object Storage provides its own API. It also provides an Amazon S3-compatible API. It is possible to upload large and large files through OCI CLI. Here we will try CloudBerry Explorer, which is a GUI tool available.&#xA;Upload files via CloudBerry Explorer Object Storage provides its own API. It also provides an Amazon S3-compatible API, so you can use existing clients for S3 as it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.6 Unmounting Block Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/6/</guid>
      <description>3.6.6 Unmounting Block Volume Unmount Connect to the Compute Instance with SSH.&#xA;Update /etc/fstab&#xA;Execute the sudo vi /etc/fstab command to delete /mnt/vol1, the volume to be unmounted, from the fstab file.&#xA;sudo vi /etc/fstab Unmount&#xA;sudo umount /mnt/vol1 Disconnect to Volume Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.&#xA;Click on the name of the target Instance you created earlier.&#xA;On the Instance detail page, click Resources &amp;gt; Attached block volumes in the lower left corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.6 Checking the Load Balancer Connection</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/6/</guid>
      <description>10.6 Check Load Balancer Connection Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking » Load Balancers.&#xA;Check the Public IP of the Load Balancer created earlier.&#xA;Connect to LB&amp;rsquo;s Public IP through a browser.&#xA;Refresh your browser.&#xA;Since the LB distribution rule is set to Round Robin, you can see that they go one by one in order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.7 Setting up an Archive via Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter07/7/</guid>
      <description>7.7 Setting up archives through lifecycle As one of the use cases of Object Storage, it is widely used for disk image backup and file backup. You are more likely to use a recent backup, but you are less likely to use a backup otherwise, but you often need to keep it for a long period of time, for example. You have a requirement that you want to reduce your Storage costs even a little bit during the retention period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.6.7 Deleting Block Volume</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/6/7/</guid>
      <description>3.6.7 Deleting Block Volume Caution Terminate the Block Volume and it will be completely deleted. Please note that this is not recoverable. Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes.&#xA;Click on the action icon next to Block Volume and then click on Terminate.&#xA;Reconfirmation&#xA;Once terminated, it cannot be recovered. If you still want to delete it, click Terminate.&#xA;Terminate complete</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
