<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>8. Using File Storage, a Network File System on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/</link><description>Recent content in 8. Using File Storage, a Network File System on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>8.1 Example File Storage Configuration</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/1/</guid><description>8.1 Example of File Storage Configuration A shared file system between servers, file storage allows multiple client servers to share files. In order to understand the necessary security rules, let&amp;rsquo;s configure File Storage on a separate subnet from the default VCN&amp;rsquo;s subnet as shown in the figure below.
Security List
In the figure below, the source IP is designated as the CIDR of the VCN to allow access from a specific subnet on the VCN.</description></item><item><title>8.2 Mounting and using FSS on a Linux VM</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/2/</guid><description>8.2 Mounting and using FSS (File Storage Service) on a Linux VM Constraints Even if File Storage is the same subnet as Compute Instance, the following rules must be set in the Security List to open the File Storage firewall. Create Subnet Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;raquo; Virtual Cloud Networks.
Click on ExampleVCN, the VCN you created earlier.
Click Create Subnets
Enter creation information: Enter only bold text fields and use default values ​​for the rest.</description></item><item><title>8.3 Export Option for Access Control</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/3/</guid><description>8.3 Export Option for Access Control Permission control through Export Option setting Move to the detail screen of the file system created earlier. Click Export created in the Export list as shown in the figure below.
At the bottom of the Export detail screen, NFS Export Options are displayed as shown in the figure.
The default created option is accessible as Read/Write from all clients (0.0.0.0/0).
Click Edit NFS Export Options.</description></item><item><title>8.4 Snapshot for Backup</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/4/</guid><description>8.4 Snapshot for backup You can create a Snapshot of the File System based on the time it was executed. You can recover files or all of them from the created Snapshot.
Snapshot #1 Connect to the tested VM.
Copy one file to the mounted file system.
[opc@examplelinuxinstance ~]$ cd /mnt/FSS-Storage/ [opc@examplelinuxinstance FSS-Storage]$wget https://github.com/oracle/oci-cli/releases/download/v3.4.2/oci-cli-3.4.2-Oracle-Linux-7.9-Offline.zip ... 2022-01-14 06:04:59 (6.24 MB/s) - ‘oci-cli-3.4.2-Oracle-Linux-7.9-Offline.zip’ saved [42528311/42528311] [opc@examplelinuxinstance FSS-Storage]$ ls -la total 43025 drwxrwxrwx. 2 root root 3 Jan 14 06:04 .</description></item></channel></rss>