<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>5. Using Security Lists to Configure Firewalls on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/</link><description>Recent content in 5. Using Security Lists to Configure Firewalls on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5.1 Installing Apache HTTP Server on Linux Instance</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/1/</guid><description>5.1 Installing Apache HTTP Server on Linux Instance Connect to the created instance through the SSH command. The commands below are based on Oracle Enterprise Linux.
ssh –i &amp;lt;private_key&amp;gt; &amp;lt;username&amp;gt;@&amp;lt;public-ip-address&amp;gt; Install Apache HTTP Server
sudo yum -y install httpd Open port 80, port for Apache HTTP in OS firewall
sudo firewall-cmd --permanent --add-port=80/tcp Tips Firewall open ports
Modify the above command according to a port other than the Apache server default port, or a port that needs to be opened when using other applications, and open the port in the firewall.</description></item><item><title>5.2 Updating the Default Security List</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/2/</guid><description>5.2 Method #1. Updating the Default Security List Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;raquo; Instances.
Click the desired instance to go to the detail page.
Click Resources &amp;raquo; Attached VNICs in the lower left.
You can see the virtual network interface card, Virtual Network Interface Card (VNIC) being used as shown in the picture. Click the Subnet to which this network card belongs. Of course, if there are multiple VNICs, it is affected by the subnet settings to which each belongs.</description></item><item><title>5.3 Adding a Custom Security List</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/3/</guid><description>5.3 Method #2. Adding a Custom Security List Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;raquo; Virtual Private Networks.
Click the VCN you are currently using (eg ExampleVCN) to go to the details of the VCN.
Go to Resources &amp;gt; Security List item in the lower left.
Click Create Security List to add Custom Security List in addition to Security for Private Subnet and Public Subnet created by VCN Wizard.</description></item><item><title>5.4 Testing Apache HTTP Server Connection</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/4/</guid><description>5.4 Apache HTTP Server Connection Test Test connection through Compute Instance running Apache HTTP Server. You can see that they are connected well as in the picture.</description></item></channel></rss>