<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Monitoring on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/monitoring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Monitoring on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>12.1 Enabling Compute Instance Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/1/</guid>
      <description>12.1 Enable Compute Instance Monitoring Enable Monitoring Below I used the latest Oracle Linux image with OracleCloudAgent already installed.&#xA;Go to the detail page of the Compute instance you want to monitor.&#xA;Select Resources &amp;gt; Metrics in the lower left&#xA;Click Enable Monitoring to enable monitoring Boot Volumes, Block Volumes, VNICs Metric information is basically collected for other services that support monitoring except Compute. Check monitoring of resources mounted on Compute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.2 Creating Monitoring Alarm</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/2/</guid>
      <description>12.2 Creating Monitoring Alarm Let&amp;rsquo;s create an alarm to send an email when CPU utilization reaches a specified number among monitoring set on Compute instance.&#xA;Defined in Observability &amp;amp; Management &amp;gt; Monitoring &amp;gt; Alarm Definition in the navigation menu in the OCI console Defined in the options menu of the resource monitoring metric There are two methods above, but in this document, we will proceed to the second method, which is easy to use because the alarm&amp;rsquo;s metric is automatically set as the selected monitoring metric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.3.1 Installing Grafana on Compute VM</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/1/</guid>
      <description>12.3.1 Install Grafana on Compute VM Create Compute Instance Go to the Compute Instance creation screen. Select the image source as the Oracle Linux Cloud Developer Image image from the Oracle Images list. Oracle Cloud Developer Image has development tools such as OCI CLI already installed. Create a Compute instance. Copy the OCID of the created Compute instance. OCI CLI - Instance Principal Settings In order to use the OCI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12.3.2 Grafana Configuration</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter12/3/2/</guid>
      <description>12.3.2 Grafana Configuration Register Data Source Log in to Grafana.&#xA;Go to left menu Configuration &amp;gt; Data Sources, or click Add data source on the home dashboard. Select Oracle Cloud Infrastructure among data sources OCI Data Source Settings&#xA;Tenancy OCID: Log in to the OCI Console, check and enter the Tenancy OCID Default Region: Select the desired Region Environment: Select OCI Instance Click Save &amp;amp; Test to check if the connection is successful.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
