<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>6. Using IAM to Set User Permissions on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/</link><description>Recent content in 6. Using IAM to Set User Permissions on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>6.1 Compartment</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/1/</guid><description>6.1 Compartment A compartment is a logical concept that makes it easy to manage resources, and you can think of it as a folder structure. When a Tenancy is created, one Root Compartment is created for the first time, and an administrator can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources belong to a specific compartment, and users&amp;rsquo; access policies can be managed in units of compartments.</description></item><item><title>6.2 Creating Users</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/2/</guid><description>6.2 Create User Tips Users who can access OCI are mainly IDCS users and OCI users. OCI is connected to Identity Cloud Service by default, so IDCS users can be federated and logged in. And IDCS is not registered, it has its own users only in OCI. The content here is intended only for users of OCI itself. Add OCI Manager Step 1. Add OCI Manager Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description></item><item><title>6.3 Creating Groups</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/3/</guid><description>6.3 Create a group Step 1. Add OCI group Log in to the OCI console as administrator. Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Identity &amp;amp; Security &amp;raquo; Identity &amp;raquo; Groups. After creating Cloud Account, you can see that there is only one Administrators group. Click Create Group Enter group information Name: Enter &amp;ldquo;SandboxGroup&amp;rdquo; Description: Enter a description, Ex) same name as &amp;ldquo;SandboxGroup&amp;rdquo; Click Create Step 2. Add User to Group Click the created group.</description></item><item><title>6.4 Creating a Policy</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/4/</guid><description>6.4 Creating Policy Step 1. Add Policy for the created group Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Identity &amp;amp; Security &amp;raquo; Identity &amp;raquo; Policies.
In the lower left, specify the target Compartment as Root Compartment.
Click Create Policy
Enter policy information
Name: Enter &amp;ldquo;SandboxPolicy&amp;rdquo;
Description: Enter a description, Ex) same name as &amp;ldquo;SandboxPolicy&amp;rdquo;
Policy Statements:
Select &amp;ldquo;Show manual editor&amp;rdquo; to input directly. Users in the SandboxGroup are set as follows to grant all permissions to the Sandbox Compartment.</description></item><item><title>6.5 Grabbing the Policy Concept</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/5/</guid><description>6.5 Getting the Policy Concept IAM Policy IAM Policy is an access policy for OCI resources. A policy can generally be thought of as defining what grants a user group permission to a specific type of resource belonging to a specific compartment.
Policy syntax All policies have the following syntax.
Allow &amp;lt;subject&amp;gt; to &amp;lt;verb&amp;gt; &amp;lt;resource-type&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;location&amp;gt; where &amp;lt;conditions&amp;gt; For detailed syntax, please refer to OCI Documentation.
https://docs.cloud.oracle.com/iaas/Content/Identity/Concepts/policysyntax.htm
Policy General Format If the permissions for resources are defined through the policy below, all permissions are granted to the administrator when creating a tenancy, and general users and groups that do not apply a separate policy have no permissions at all.</description></item></channel></rss>