<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security list on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/security-list/</link><description>Recent content in security list on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/security-list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>8.2 Mounting and using FSS on a Linux VM</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter08/2/</guid><description>8.2 Mounting and using FSS (File Storage Service) on a Linux VM Constraints Even if File Storage is the same subnet as Compute Instance, the following rules must be set in the Security List to open the File Storage firewall. Create Subnet Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;gt; Virtual Cloud Networks.
Click on ExampleVCN, the VCN you created earlier.
Click Create Subnets
Enter creation information: Enter only bold text fields and use default values ​​for the rest.</description></item><item><title>5.2 Updating the Default Security List</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/2/</guid><description>5.2 Method #1. Updating the Default Security List Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.
Click the desired instance to go to the detail page.
Click Resources &amp;gt; Attached VNICs in the lower left.
You can see the virtual network interface card, Virtual Network Interface Card (VNIC) being used as shown in the picture. Click the Subnet to which this network card belongs. Of course, if there are multiple VNICs, it is affected by the subnet settings to which each belongs.</description></item><item><title>5.3 Adding a Custom Security List</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter05/3/</guid><description>5.3 Method #2. Adding a Custom Security List Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;gt; Virtual Private Networks.
Click the VCN you are currently using (eg ExampleVCN) to go to the details of the VCN.
Go to Resources &amp;gt; Security List item in the lower left.
Click Create Security List to add Custom Security List in addition to Security for Private Subnet and Public Subnet created by VCN Wizard.</description></item></channel></rss>