<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>3.7 Utilizing Block Volume Backups on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/</link><description>Recent content in 3.7 Utilizing Block Volume Backups on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3.7.1 Backing up Block Volumes</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/1/</guid><description>3.7.1 Backing up Block Volume Full If you deleted the Block Volume in the previous guide, create it again.
Backing up the default Block Volume Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes.
Click the name of the Block Volume you want to back up.
On the Block Volume detail page, click Resources &amp;gt; Block Volume Backups in the lower left corner.</description></item><item><title>3.7.2 Creating a New Volume from Backup</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/2/</guid><description>3.7.2 Create a new volume with backup This is a recovery method that creates a new Block Volume using the Block Volume backup. The restored Block Volume can be used by mounting it on the Compute Instance in the same way as installing a new Block Volume.
Create a new Block Volume from backup Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes Backups.</description></item><item><title>3.7.3 Copying Backups to Another Region</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/3/</guid><description>3.7.3 Copying Backup to Another Region Block Volume backup is only possible within a single Region. If it is needed in another region for disaster recovery or other purposes, it can be copied to another region through the inter-region copy function.
Constraints Cross-region backup copies have some limitations. See the official documentation for exact details.
Limitations for Copying Volume Backups Across Regions Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Storage &amp;gt; Block Volumes Backups.</description></item><item><title>3.7.4 Backing up Policy-Based Block Volumes</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/7/4/</guid><description>3.7.4 Backing up policy-based block volumes Volume Backup Policies Bronze Policy
Monthly - Monthly incremental backups run on the first day of each month. It is maintained for 12 months. Every year - A full backup is executed on January 1st of each year. It is maintained for 5 years. Silver Policy
Weekly - Weekly incremental backups run every Sunday. It is preserved for 4 weeks. Monthly - Monthly incremental backups run on the first day of each month.</description></item></channel></rss>