<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oci User on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/oci-user/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oci User on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/oci-user/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3.1 Creating a Work Compartment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/1/</guid>
      <description>3.1 Creating a Work Compartment A compartment can be thought of as a folder structure as a logical concept that makes it easy to manage resources. When a tenancy is created, the first Root Compartment is created, and administrators can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources fall into a specific Compartment and can manage the access policies of their users in units of Compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.2 Creating Users</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter06/2/</guid>
      <description>6.2 Create User Tips Users who can access OCI are mainly IDCS users and OCI users. OCI is connected to Identity Cloud Service by default, so IDCS users can be federated and logged in. And IDCS is not registered, it has its own users only in OCI. The content here is intended only for users of OCI itself. Add OCI Manager Step 1. Add OCI Manager Open the navigation menu in the OCI console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14.2.6 Example, Creating Users Using List and Count</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter14/3/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter14/3/6/</guid>
      <description>14.2.6 Example, creating a user using list and count When creating resources, there are cases where multiple identical resources are created through Array. Considering the situation where multiple users are created to compose the practice environment, let&amp;rsquo;s see how to create multiple users at once through list and count.&#xA;Policy required for user creation Allow group &amp;lt;group_name&amp;gt; to manage users in tenancy Create User OCI users can be created using the syntax oci_identity_user.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
