<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3. Use the OCI Compute VM on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3. Use the OCI Compute VM on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3.1 Creating a Work Compartment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/1/</guid>
      <description>3.1 Creating a Work Compartment A compartment can be thought of as a folder structure as a logical concept that makes it easy to manage resources. When a tenancy is created, the first Root Compartment is created, and administrators can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources fall into a specific Compartment and can manage the access policies of their users in units of Compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.2 Creating a VCN for a Virtual Network Environment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/2/</guid>
      <description>3.2 Creating a VCN for a Virtual Network Environment What is a Virtual Cloud Network (VCN)? Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) provides a virtual network environment. You can configure the VCN and its resources to suit your needs, thus configuring several forms of virtual network environment. A subnet is created as a sub-element of a VCN as a unit of a single Availability Domain. Depending on the route table, subnets move traffic to the destination path, and subnets can control incoming and outgoing traffic to the security list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.3 Creating a Key Pair for SSH Connections</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/3/</guid>
      <description>3.3 Creating a Key Pair for SSH Connections Use SSH Key Pair instead of password to access the server instance. Key pair consists of a private key and a public key, the private key is kept on the user&amp;rsquo;s computer, and the public key must be registered when the server instance is created.&#xA;To create a key pair, you need a key generation tool, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you&amp;rsquo;ll use it after installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.4 Creating a Linux Instance</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/4/</guid>
      <description>3.4 Creating a Linux Instance tip It is a good idea to proactively check for sufficient resources before creating the instance. A Service Limit lookup is used to determine if there are resources available, particularly CPUs available, before creating an instance. In the OCI Console, open the navigation menu. Navigate to the Compute &amp;gt; Instances topic.&#xA;Verify the Region where you want to create the instance and click Create Instance.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
