<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>virtual cloud network on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/virtual-cloud-network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in virtual cloud network on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/virtual-cloud-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3.2 Creating a VCN for a Virtual Network Environment</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/2/</guid>
      <description>3.2 Creating a VCN for a Virtual Network Environment What is a Virtual Cloud Network (VCN)? Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) provides a virtual network environment. You can configure the VCN and its resources to suit your needs, thus configuring several forms of virtual network environment. A subnet is created as a sub-element of a VCN as a unit of a single Availability Domain. Depending on the route table, subnets move traffic to the destination path, and subnets can control incoming and outgoing traffic to the security list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.4 Virtual Cloud Network(VCN)</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/4/</guid>
      <description>1.4 Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) When you use OCI, one of the first things you need to do is create a Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) for other cloud resources. A virtual network environment that is used by server resources in Oracle data centers, such as network address allocation, firewalls, routing rules, gateways, and so on.
If you configure the auto-created method when you first create your VCN, the following default configuration will be created:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
