<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Boot Volume on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/boot-volume/</link><description>Recent content in Boot Volume on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/boot-volume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3.8.1 Backing Up Boot Volume</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/1/</guid><description>3.8.1 Backing up Boot Volume The Boot Volume backup function is almost identical to the Block Volume backup function.
Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to the Boot Volume detail page.
Method #1 Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances. Click the target instance VM. Go to Resources &amp;gt; Boot volume and click the Attached Boot Volume to go to the detail page. Method #2 Go to Storage &amp;gt; Block Volume.</description></item><item><title>3.8.2 Creating a New Boot Volume from a Backup</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/2/</guid><description>3.8.2 Create a new Boot Volume from backup The Boot Volume backup recovery function is almost identical to the Block Volume backup recovery function.
Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to the Boot Volume detail page.
On the Boot Volume detail page, click Resources &amp;gt; Boot Volume Backups in the lower left corner.
Click Restore Boot Volume in the action menu on the right of the desired backup.</description></item><item><title>3.8.3 Creating a New Instance with Boot Volume</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter03/8/3/</guid><description>3.8.3 Creating a New Instance with Boot Volume You can create a new Compute Instance using a Boot Volume that is not already in use for the Instance.
Create a new instance with Boot Volume Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute &amp;gt; Instances.
Check the Region to create an instance for and click Create Instance.
Choose the image you want to use
Click Edit in Image and Shape to change the image source.</description></item></channel></rss>