<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>resource manage on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/resource-manage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in resource manage on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/resource-manage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>15.1 Using the Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/1/</guid>
      <description>15.1 Using Resource Manager Resource Manager is a service that registers and runs Terraform Configuration as a function to automate OCI resource provisioning. Instead of installing Terraform on the client, you can register Terraform Configuration files in Resource Manager and run it with the OCI console or OCI CLI.
The difference is that the Terraform CLI does not need to be installed separately, and the Terraform execution state is managed by the Resource Manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15.2 Stack Template for Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/2/</guid>
      <description>15.2 Stack Template for Resource Manager Stack Template   In the OCI console, click Developer Services &amp;raquo; Resource Manager &amp;raquo; Stacks in the navigation menu.
  Click Create Stack.
  Select the second Template option and click Select Template.
   You can see the templates we are providing.
  Quickstarts
   Service
   Architect
   Private
   It is empty for now, but you can use the template to be shared within Tenancy by registering a private template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15.3 Configuring a Private Git Server for Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter15/3/</guid>
      <description>15.3 Configuring Private Git Server for Resource Manager Resource Manager supports GitHub and GitLab as Terraform configuration repositories. Environments that can be accessed through the public Internet can of course be connected from Resource Manager. If you want to use an internal server instead of a public server for setting storage, you can connect to a privately installed server on OCI by following the procedure below.
Create Private GitLab CE VM Create Compute instance   Create a Compute instance on which to install GitLab CE.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
