<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>verrazzano on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/verrazzano/</link><description>Recent content in verrazzano on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/verrazzano/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>6.1 Installing Verrazzano</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/1.install-verrazzano/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/1.install-verrazzano/</guid><description>6.1 Installing Verrazzano on a Kubernetes cluster Preparing the Kubernetes cluster Verrazzano is a way to install on a Kubernetes cluster using the Kubernetes Operator method. In other words, you need a Kubernetes cluster to install on. Here we proceed based on the OKE cluster.
Preparing the Container Engine for Kubernetes (OKE) cluster Create an OKE cluster with default settings in Quick Create mode.
Prepare an environment with sufficient capacity to deploy all components and example applications on Verrazzano.</description></item><item><title>6.2 Understanding the Open Application Model and Deploying Applications</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/2.deploy-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/2.deploy-app/</guid><description>6.2 Understanding the Open Application Model and deploying applications Reference
https://verrazzano.io/latest/docs/guides/app-deployment/application-deployment-guide/ Open Application Model The Open Application Model (OAM) is a model that seeks to enable developers to focus on their applications rather than containers or orchestrators or infrastructure. In order to deploy an application as a container on Kubernetes, in addition to deployment, various resources must be deployed for additional settings such as monitoring and traffic handling, and YAML files must be defined accordingly.</description></item><item><title>6.3 Installing Multicluster Verrazzano</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/3.multicluster-verrazzano/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/3.multicluster-verrazzano/</guid><description>6.3 Installing Multicluster Verrazzano reference document
https://verrazzano.io/latest/docs/applications/multicluster/ Install Verrazzano Install Verrazzano on admin-cluster Installing Verrazzano in a single cluster environment is the same as installing it. dev or prod Install as profile. However, the environment name is specified in the installation yaml file (eg, install-oci.yaml) to distinguish it from managed-cluster.
example
... spec: environmentName: admin profile: dev ... Install Verrazzano on managed-cluster Installing Verrazzano in a single cluster environment is the same as installing it.</description></item><item><title>6.4 Deploying Applications to Multicluster</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/4.deploy-app-to-multicluster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/4.deploy-app-to-multicluster/</guid><description>6.4 Deploying Applications to Multicluster Deploy the Helidon sample application We have seen earlier that Java applications developed using the Helidon framework are deployed in Verrazzano using the Open Application Model. I&amp;rsquo;ve verified that I&amp;rsquo;m deploying against a single Kubernetes cluster.
This time, let&amp;rsquo;s check the deployment in a multi-cluster environment. Verrazzano is deployed against three clusters.
Admin Cluster admin-cluster Managed Cluster managed-cluster-1 managed-cluster-2 Application Deployment Create namespace
Based on single cluster (reference)</description></item><item><title>6.5 Deploying WebLogic Server to OKE via Verrazzano</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/5.weblogic-on-oke-using-verrazzano/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/5.weblogic-on-oke-using-verrazzano/</guid><description>6.5 Deploying WebLogic Server to OKE via Verrazzano When installing Verrazzano, WebLogic Operator is installed together. This content follows and organizes the contents in the document below, and describes how to use it if you want to migrate the application that is deployed and used from the existing on-premise to the WebLogic Server to the Kubernetes environment without modifying the WebLogic Server as a whole. content.
https://verrazzano.io/latest/docs/guides/lift-and-shift/lift-and-shift/ The procedure to perform is as follows.</description></item><item><title>6. Using the Enterprise Container Platform Verrazzano</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/verrazzano/</guid><description>6. Using Verrazzano Verrazzano is an open-source platform that supports running traditional and cloud-native applications in a Kubernetes environment, and includes various open-source components for each role.
Verrazzano main features as stated in the Verrazzano documentation:
Hybrid and multicluster workload management Special handling for WebLogic, Coherence, and Helidon applications Multicluster infrastructure management Integrated and pre-wired application monitoring Integrated security DevOps and GitOps enablement reference document
https://verrazzano.io/latest/docs/ https://verrazzano.io/latest/docs/setup/versions/#installed-components</description></item></channel></rss>