<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1. OCI Basic Concept on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/</link><description>Recent content in 1. OCI Basic Concept on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1.1 Regions, Availability Domains</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/1/</guid><description>1.1 Regions, Availability Domains Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI) is hosted in Region and Availability Domain. Region is a geographical area and Availability Domain is a data center located in one region. A single Region consists of one or more Availability Domain.
Availability domains are separated from each other so that they are not affected by defects at the same time or by defects in other Availability domains.Availability Domain is designed so that it does not affect other Availability domains because it does not share resources such as power, cooling and internal networks.</description></item><item><title>1.2 Fault Domains</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/2/</guid><description>1.2 Fault Domains A Fault Domain is a grouping of hardware and infrastructure within an Availability Domain. Each Availability Domain has three Fault Domains. Fault Domains ensure that compute instances are not distributed across one physical hardware within a single Availability Domain. Hardware failures or hardware maintenance within one Fault Domain do not affect other Fault Domains.
When creating a new Compute instance, users can select a Fault Domain. If not selected by the user, the system automatically assigns them.</description></item><item><title>1.3 Compartment</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/3/</guid><description>1.3 Compartment Compartments are a folder structure that makes it easy to manage resources. When a tenancy is created, the first Root Compartment is created, and administrators can add a new Compartment as a child of the Root Compartment. All OCI resources fall into a specific Compartment and can manage the access policies of their users in units of Compartment.</description></item><item><title>1.4 Virtual Cloud Network(VCN)</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/4/</guid><description>1.4 Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) When you use OCI, one of the first things you need to do is create a Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) for other cloud resources. A virtual network environment that is used by server resources in Oracle data centers, such as network address allocation, firewalls, routing rules, gateways, and so on.
If you configure the auto-created method when you first create your VCN, the following default configuration will be created:</description></item><item><title>1.5 Bare Metal, Virtual Machine</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/5/</guid><description>1.5 Bare Metal, Virtual Machine OCI offers both Bare Metal and Virtual Machine instances
Bare Metal: Provides an environment where physical servers can be dedicated to a single user. By using the resources of the physical server directly and dedicatedly, we utilize 100% of the server resources to deliver high performance. Virtual Machine: Provides a computing environment through virtualization on a physical server. By going through a layer virtualized by the hypervisor, it offers relatively lower performance than bare metal.</description></item><item><title>1.6 Map of offerings between cloud service providers</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter01/6/</guid><description>1.6 Map of offerings between cloud service providers To help you understand the cloud services offered by Oracle Cloud Infrastructure as of IaaS, map with the service names of third-party Amazon Web Services (AWS), Microsoft Azure, and Google Cloud Platform to the following as of the Oracle Cloud site:
Cloud Service Mapping official site Mapping Cloud Services Category Oracle Cloud Infrastructure AWS Azure Google Regions Availability Domain (AD) Availability Zone (AZ) Availability Zone (AZ) Zones Networking &amp;amp; Content Delivery Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Virtual Cloud Network (VCN) Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Virtual Network Virtual Private Cloud Networking &amp;amp; Content Delivery Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Load Balancing Elastic Load Balancing Load Balancer ; Application Gateway Cloud Load Balancing Networking &amp;amp; Content Delivery Oracle Cloud Infrastructure FastConnect AWS Direct Connect Azure ExpressRoute Cloud Interconnect Compute Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Compute - Virtual Machines Amazon EC2 Azure Virtual Machines Compute Engine Compute Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Compute - Bare Metal Amazon EC2 - I3.</description></item></channel></rss>