<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Load Balancer on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/load-balancer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Load Balancer on TheKoguryo&#39;s Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/load-balancer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10.1 Load Balancer Configuration Example</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/1/</guid>
      <description>10.1 Load Balancer configuration example To ensure the availability of instances, you can load balance across multiple target servers via OCI Load Balancer. Target servers are also typically configured in different ADs or in different Fault Domains on the same AD to ensure availability. And the OCI Load Balancer itself is configured redundantly for Fail Over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.2 VCN Configuration</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/2/</guid>
      <description>10.2 VCN Configuration Create VCN for LoadBalancer test Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking » Virtual Cloud Networks.&#xA;In the lower left compartment, click Sandbox.&#xA;Click Start VCN Wizard&#xA;Select Create VCN with Internet Connectivity and click Start VCN Wizard again&#xA;As described in the figure, the selected one includes Public and Private Subnet, and communicates with the Internet through Internat Gateway and NAT Gateway, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.3 Creating a Backend Web Server</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/3/</guid>
      <description>10.3 Creating a Backend Web Server Create your first Linux Instance Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Compute » Instances.&#xA;Check the Region to create an instance for and click Create Instance.&#xA;Enter creation information&#xA;Enter the necessary values ​​for only the main items and accept the default values ​​for the rest.&#xA;Basic Information&#xA;Name: Enter a name, for example “Webserver1” Create in compartment: Select the compartment to be located, select the previously created Sandbox Image and Shape</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.4 Creating a Subnet for a Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/4/</guid>
      <description>10.4 Create Subnet for Load Balancer Create Subnet Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking » Virtual Cloud Networks.&#xA;Click LoadBalancerVCN, the VCN you created earlier.&#xA;Click Create Subnets&#xA;Enter creation information: Enter only bold text fields and use default values ​​for the rest.&#xA;Name: Enter a name, Public LB Subnet Subnet Type: Select the default REGIONAL REGIONAL: This is a subnet that is globally located in the region, and has the advantage of being able to use the IP as it is in case of a Failover to another AD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.5 Creating a Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/5/</guid>
      <description>10.5 Creating a Load Balancer Create Load Balancer Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking &amp;gt; Load Balancers.&#xA;Click Create Load Balancer.&#xA;Select Load Balancer as the type.&#xA;Load Balancer Type: Used when distributing to HTTP listeners as L7 load balancers. Network Load Balancer Type: L4 load balancer, used to distribute to general IP and Port. Enter basic creation information&#xA;Name: Enter Load Balancer name, Ex) ExampleLB</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.6 Checking the Load Balancer Connection</title>
      <link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oci/chapter10/6/</guid>
      <description>10.6 Check Load Balancer Connection Open the navigation menu in the OCI console. Go to Networking » Load Balancers.&#xA;Check the Public IP of the Load Balancer created earlier.&#xA;Connect to LB&amp;rsquo;s Public IP through a browser.&#xA;Refresh your browser.&#xA;Since the LB distribution rule is set to Round Robin, you can see that they go one by one in order.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
