<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>appdev on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/appdev/</link><description>Recent content in appdev on TheKoguryo's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko-kr</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/tags/appdev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>7.1 Developing Spring Boot applications</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/appdev/1.develop-spring-boot-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/appdev/1.develop-spring-boot-app/</guid><description>7.1 Developing Spring Boot applications Based on the Spring Boot example, check out the process of app development, container image build, and deployment to OKE.
Create a Spring Boot-based microservice Spring Initializr is used to develop based on the basic project source file.
Create a project file through Spring Initializr.
Method 1. Create a basic project source file using Spring Initializr.
As shown in the figure below, enter project information and click Generate to generate source files.</description></item><item><title>7.2.1 Creating a GraalVM-based container image</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/appdev/2.graalvm/1.use-graal-vm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/appdev/2.graalvm/1.use-graal-vm/</guid><description>7.2.1 Creating a GraalVM-based container image In this article, we will look at how to improve the performance of Java applications without code changes in the simplest way through an improved just-in-time (JIT) compiler.
Container image provided by GraalVM GraalVM provides an open source community version and a commercial enterprise version. The Enterprise version offers higher optimization capabilities. GraalVM is included in the Oracle Java SE subscription model and is available at no cost to resources within Oracle Cloud Infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>7. Developing Applications</title><link>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/appdev/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thekoguryo.github.io/en/oracle-cloudnative/appdev/</guid><description>7. Developing applications</description></item></channel></rss>